hisilicon.com 2019-11-28

# Privacy | HiSilicon

HiSilicon(Shanghai) Technologies CO.,LIMITED. (hereinafter referred to as "HiSilicon," "we," "us," or "our") fully respects your privacy. Therefore, we have developed this Privacy Statement (hereinafter referred to as "this Statement"), which describes how we collect, use, disclose, protect, store, and transfer your personal data. Please read this Statement carefully and let us know if you have any questions.

Personal data refers to any electronic or other information which alone or jointly with other information can be used to identify a natural person or make him/her identifiable. This Statement explains how HiSilicon processes your personal data, but does not cover all processing scenarios, as you will be informed in advance of specific processing activities. Therefore, before using a specific product or service, read its privacy statement or supplementary statement.

This Statement applies only to HiSilicon products and services, including but not limited to surveillance, mobile cam, set top box, display, home network, NB-IoT, Kirin Balong, HiKey, and Ascend.

This Statement describes:

1\. How HiSilicon Collects and Uses Your Personal Data

2\. How HiSilicon Uses Cookies and Similar Technologies

3\. How HiSilicon Shares Your Personal Data

4\. How HiSilicon Protects Your Personal Data

5\. How You Can Manage Your Personal Data

6\. How HiSilicon Protects Children's Personal Data

7\. Links to Third-Party Websites, Products, and Services

8\. International Transfers of Your Personal Data

9\. Updates to This Statement

10\. How to Contact Us

###  I. How HiSilicon Collects and Uses Your Personal Data 

A. Personal Data Collected by HiSilicon: Before using HiSilicon products or services, you may need to provide personal data. You do not have to provide your personal data to HiSilicon, but failing to do so prevents us from providing you with certain products or services. HiSilicon collects and uses your personal data only for the purposes stated in this Statement. Here are some examples of personal data we may collect:

1\. Personal data that you provide to HiSilicon: Some functions or services require personal data, such as your name, email address, mobile number, company name, and address.

2\. Information from third-party sources: When permitted by law, HiSilicon collects information about you from public and commercial sources. HiSilicon may collect other information about you, your devices, or your use of services in other ways. Collection details will be explained to you at the time of collection, or data is collected after you consent.

3\. In the following cases, HiSilicon will collect and use your personal information without your authorization:

(1) Related to national security and national defense 

(2) Related to public security, public health, and major public interests

(3) Related to criminal investigation, prosecution, trial, and judgment execution

(4) For the purpose of safeguarding the vital legal rights and interests such as life and property of personal information subjects or other individuals (while it is difficult to obtain the consent from the personal information subjects or other individuals)

(5) The collected personal information is disclosed to the public by the personal information subject.

(6) Personal information is collected from legally disclosed information sources, such as news reports and information disclosed by governments.

(7) Required for signing contracts according to your requirements

(8) Required for maintaining secure and stable operations of provided products or services, such as the discovery and removal of the product and service faults

(9) Required for legitimate news reporting

(10) Required by an academic research institute which conducts statistical or academic research in the public interest and provides the research results publicly. Personal data in the results will be anonymized.

(11) Other situations prescribed by laws and regulations

4\. Collection and use of non-identifiable data: Non-identifiable data refers to data that cannot be used to identify an individual, for example statistics on website visits. HiSilicon will collect non-identifiable data to understand how users use our products and services. This allows us to improve our services to better meet your requirements. HiSilicon may decide to collect, use, disclose, and transfer non-identifiable data for other purposes.

How HiSilicon Uses Your Personal Data

HiSilicon may use your personal data for the following purposes:

1\. Deliver your requested products and services, or provide technical support and services based on your requirements.

2\. Provide personalized user experience and content.

### II. How HiSilicon Uses Cookies and Similar Technologies

HiSilicon's website and online services may use local storage technologies such as cookies, pixel tags/web beacons. HiSilicon regards the information collected through cookies and similar technologies as non-personal information. However, if local laws or regulations regard the IP addresses or similar data points as personal information, HiSilicon will also regard these identification marks as personal information.

A. Cookie: A cookie is a text file stored by a web server on a computer or mobile device. Its content can be retrieved and read only by the server that created it. Cookies are unique to the browser or mobile application you are using. The text in a cookie often consists of identifiers, site names, and numbers and characters.

Sometimes, HiSilicon stores cookies on computers for the purpose of improving user experience, including the following scenarios:

(1) Personalization cookies: Storage of your preferences and settings. A website can use cookies to save settings, such as your language setting and font size, items in your shopping cart, and other browser preferences, on your computer or mobile device.

(2) Statistical cookies: With cookies, HiSilicon can collect information about your use of our website and other applications, either for a single visit (using a session cookie) or for repeated visits (using a persistent cookie).

HiSilicon uses cookies only the purposes described in this Statement. You can manage or delete cookies as you wish. For details, see AboutCookies.org. You can clear all cookies stored on your computer, and most up-to-date web browsers provide the option of preventing cookie storage. However, preventing cookies will require you to change your user settings every time you visit our website. Find out how to manage cookie settings for your browser here:[Internet Explorer ](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) > [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) > [ Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Cookies) > [Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?locale=en_US&viewlocale=en_US) > [Opera](https://help.opera.com/en/latest/).

If you clear cookies, you will need to reconfigure your settings the next time you visit a HiSilicon website. Note that some HiSilicon services require the use of cookies, and disabling cookies may affect your use of some or all functions of these services.

B.Other Local Storage

HiSilicon and some third parties may use other local storage technologies, for example, local shared objects ("Flash cookies") and HTML5 local storage. Similar to cookies, these technologies store information on your device and can record some information about your activities and preferences. However, these technologies may use different media from cookies. Therefore, you may not be able to control them using your browser tools and settings. For details about how to disable or delete information contained in Flash cookies, click [Here](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html).

C. Do Not Track

Many web browsers provide a Do Not Track function that can release Do Not Track requests to websites. Major Internet standardization organizations have not established policies specifying how websites should handle these requests. If you enable Do Not Track in your browser, all HiSilicon websites will respect your selection.

### III.How HiSilicon Shares Your Personal Data

We will share your personal data with other companies, organizations and individuals only in the following circumstances:

1\. Sharing with consent: With your consent, HiSilicon will share the information that you have authorized with specified third parties.

2\. Sharing pursuant to laws and regulations: HiSilicon will share your information as required by laws and regulations, for resolving legal disputes, or as required by administrative or judicial authorities pursuant to law.

In the following situations, HiSilicon will share, transfer, and disclose your personal information without your prior consent: 

(1) Related to national security and national defense 

(2) Related to public security, public health, and major public interests

(3) Related to criminal investigation, prosecution, trial, and judgment execution

(4) For the purpose of safeguarding the vital legal rights and interests such as life and property of personal information subjects or other individuals (while it is difficult to obtain the consent from the personal information subjects or other individuals)

(5) The collected personal information is disclosed to the public by the personal information subject.

(6) Personal information is collected from legally disclosed information sources, such as news reports and information disclosed by governments.

According to laws and regulations, HiSilicon will not notify you of the sharing and transfer of your anonymized data (which cannot be restored to re-identify you), nor will we obtain your consent.

### IV. How HiSilicon Protects Your Personal Data

HiSilicon takes the security of your personal data seriously and has adopted standard industry practices to protect your personal data and prevent it from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, modification, damage, or loss. To protect your personal data, HiSilicon takes the following measures:

(1) We take reasonable measures to ensure that all personal data we collect is minimal and relevant to the purposes for which they are processed. We retain your personal data for no longer than is necessary for the purposes stated in this Statement, unless another retention period is required or permitted by law.

(2) We use a range of technologies such as cryptography to ensure data confidentiality during transmission. We implement trusted protection mechanisms to protect data and its storage servers from attack.

(3) We deploy access control mechanisms to ensure that only authorized personnel can access your personal data. In addition, we control the number of authorized personnel and implement hierarchical permission management based on service requirements and personnel levels. Each access to personal data is logged, and logs are regularly reviewed by the administrator.

(4) We strictly select business partners and service providers and incorporate personal data protection requirements into commercial contracts, audits, and appraisals.

(5) We hold security and privacy protection training courses, tests, and publicity activities to raise employees' awareness. HiSilicon is committed to protecting your personal data. Nevertheless, no security measure is perfect and no product, service, website, data transfer, computing system, or network connection is absolutely secure.

To cope with possible risks, such as personal data leakage, damage, and loss, HiSilicon has developed several mechanisms and measures, clearly defined the rating standards of security incidents and vulnerabilities and corresponding procedures, and established a dedicated Security Advisory and Security Notice page. HiSilicon has established a dedicated emergency response team to implement security planning, loss reduction, analysis, locating, and remediation. The team also performs tracking operations with related departments based on security incident handling regulations and requirements.

If any personal data incident occurs, HiSilicon will notify you, pursuant to relevant legal and regulatory requirements, of the basics of the security incident and its possible impacts. Moreover, we will explain measures that HiSilicon has taken or will take, suggestions about active defense and risk mitigation, and remedial measures. The notification may be by email, text message, push notification, etc. If it is difficult to notify data subjects one by one, we will appropriately release a security notice. In addition, we will also report the handling status of personal data security incidents as required by supervisory authorities.

### V.How You Can Manage Your Personal Data

A. Access, rectification, deletion, portability, restriction of processing, and objection to processing.

Legislation in some countries and regions in which HiSilicon provides products or services, or from where HiSilicon processes personal data, gives data subjects the rights to access, correct, delete, or port their personal data, or submit requests of restricting or objecting to the processing of their data. 

1\. Requesting modes and channels

Data subjects' requests must be submitted through HiSilicon designated privacy channels. Requests are valid regardless of whether the requester specifies the laws on which the requests are based. Data subjects can send requests to support@hisilicon.com 

2\. Validity of requests

Most laws require that data subjects comply with specific requirements when initiating requests. This Statement requires data subjects to:

(1) Send requests through the HiSilicon dedicated request submission channel (support@hisilicon.com).

(2) Provide sufficient information for HiSilicon to verify their identity (to ensure the person who initiates the requests is the corresponding data subject or is authorized by them).

(3) Ensure that their requests are specific and feasible.

Under some circumstances, provided by laws and regulations, HiSilicon does not have to comply with the request in full or at all. 

(4) Consent withdrawal. You can change the authorized personal data collection scope or withdraw your consent without affecting the lawfulness of the processing activities based on the consent granted prior to such withdraw.

B. Deregistering a HiSilicon account

You can deregister your account in HiSilicon account-related products. After you deregister your account, we will stop providing you with products and services, and delete your personal data unless otherwise stipulated by law. Your account cannot be restored after deregistration. To start using HiSilicon products or services again, you need to register for a new account. 

### VI. How HiSilicon Protects Children's Personal Data

HiSilicon's personal and home products are intended for adults. However, when children use HiSilicon products or services, we take extra preventive measures to protect their privacy and security. HiSilicon identifies whether data subjects are children based on the age of majority defined by local laws.

When a child's personal data is collected after obtaining the consent of their parent or guardian, we will only use or disclose the information as permitted by law, as explicitly consented to by the child's parent or guardian, or as required to protect the child. If we find that personal information of children was collected without appropriate consent, we will try to delete the relevant content immediately. Parents or guardians who need to access, modify, or delete a child's personal data can contact us via the channels provided in section "How HiSilicon Protects Your Personal Data."

### VII. Links to Third-Party Websites, Products, and Services

Products and services on HiSilicon websites may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. All such links are provided for users' convenience only. HiSilicon has no control over such third parties and does not provide any explicit or implicit warranties for linked content. Such links do not constitute HiSilicon's recommendation or authorization of linked content. HiSilicon cannot control the privacy or data protection policies of third parties, and such parties are not subject to this Statement.

You must independently determine your interaction, if any, with such links. Before submitting your personal data to third parties, please read their privacy policies. HiSilicon takes no responsibility for the outcome of any interaction with third parties. 

### VIII. International Transfers of Your Personal Data

As a global company, your personal data collected by HiSilicon may be processed or accessed in the country/region where you use our products and services or in other countries/regions where HiSilicon or its service providers or business partners have a presence. These jurisdictions may have different or even no data protection laws. In such circumstances, HiSilicon will take measures to ensure that your data is processed as required by applicable laws and regulations. For example, HiSilicon requests your consent on international transfers of your personal data or implements security measures such as data anonymization before international transfers. For users in Mainland China, your personal data is stored on servers in Mainland China.

### IX. Updates to This Statement

HiSilicon reserves the right to update this Statement at any time.

Should this Statement be revised, HiSilicon will release a change notice on various channels, for example, posting the latest version on our official website: http://www.hisilicon.com. For major changes, we will also provide apparent notice (such as publicity on HiSilicon's official website or even pushing them through pop-up messages).

"Major changes" in this Statement include but are not limited to:

(1) Major changes in our service modes, for example, purposes of personal data processing, types of processed personal data, and ways of using personal data

(2) Major changes in our ownership structure, organizational structure, etc., for example, ownership changes caused by business adjustment, bankruptcy, or merger or acquisition

(3) Changes in the main objects of personal data sharing, transfer, or disclosure

(4) Major changes in your rights regarding personal data processing and the ways in which you can enjoy those rights

(5) Changes to HiSilicon departments, contacts, and complaint channels responsible for personal data processing security 

(6) High risks identified in personal data security impact assessment reports

### X. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about HiSilicon’s Privacy Policy or you would like to contact our European Data Protection representative, please contact us by email at privacy_device_ic@hisilicon.com. If you think that we are not processing your personal data in accordance with this Statement or the applicable data protection laws, you can lodge a complaint with your data protection authority, or the Cyberspace Administration of China）. Our address: [Room 101, 318 Shuxiu Road, Jinze Town, Qingpu District, Shanghai] .

Copyright © 2019 HiSilicon(Shanghai) Technologies CO.,LIMITED. All rights reserved.
